{
    "subject": "resource/The_Devil's_Own",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1990s_crime_thriller_films",
    "human_readable": "The Devil's Own is a subject of the category 1990s crime thriller films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8299002647399902,
            "question": "Give an example of a film from the 1990s crime thriller genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7789490818977356,
            "question": "Name another movie that fits the '1990s crime thriller' category."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6729437112808228,
            "question": "What type of film is 'The Devil's Own'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5739046931266785,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Devil's Own'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49752360582351685,
            "question": "Can you describe the plot of 'The Devil's Own'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41403910517692566,
            "question": "What are some common themes in crime thrillers from the 1990s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39427828788757324,
            "question": "In what decade was 'The Devil's Own' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3871982991695404,
            "question": "What elements make a film a successful crime thriller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36650586128234863,
            "question": "Who are some well-known actors who starred in 1990s crime thrillers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2679903507232666,
            "question": "What impact did 1990s crime thrillers have on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Devil's Own is a subject of the category 1990s crime thriller films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4515_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some well-known actors who starred in 1990s crime thrillers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4515_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What elements make a film a successful crime thriller?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4515_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what decade was 'The Devil's Own' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4515_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4515_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query seems to be asking whether the information in the provided context supports the statement that \"The Devil's Own is a subject of the category 1990s crime thriller films\".\n\nHere is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention \"The Devil's Own\" as a film, and in one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4515/re-ranker-msmarco/147.txt), it is described as part of the decade for film that includes thrillers."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information discusses \"The Devil's Own,\" which is described as a film from the 1990s that fits into the crime thriller genre. Therefore, the statement \"The Devil's Own is a subject of the category 1990s crime thriller films\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}